Hello friends, welcome to the new video.
In this video, I am bringing a
review of ICC Bank, whether you should
open an account with ICC Bank or not. If you
open one, what
benefits are available here. In this video, if
you are at the end, you will definitely see whether
you should open an account with this bank or
not or should invest in some other bank. So,
let's start the video.
First of all, you have ICC Bank, you have this
background, two opposite investments, if you
need funds, credit cards, everything,
you have ICC Bank. If you
settle down,
you get all the services inside it. So,
what is inside it, the
service level that you get in ICC Bank is the next
service, see that service, this is
savings account, current account, credit card,
personal loan. So, solid servicing. There are
many group companies which if you compete with each other, then it is
considered a service. For example, if
you need a health policy, then there is investment near this look garden, then there is
potential,
that service is more like roti, such
diet, if you want to go to the share market, then there is
service for that, so
you do not get the service of all the methods there, so today's
In the date, if the husband is one and if
you see inside this, you start with the savings account, he
also has a basic salary account of 10,000, it starts from 10,000,
then there is a bank account from Silvat, there is a
gold saving account on it, there is
also an account from Titanium, there is wealth
management, if it is high profile then they
have private banking, so there are all kinds of
services, if you want to open an account like them, then
you want to open that type of service here, according to that you want to open an account and
this bangal is the best option right now that if
you open an account and if you keep it, then
in the future you have any financial requirement,
free approved plated
service has started coming home a lot today,
so in the bank, for example, in case you have opened an
account in such a bank and you are
maintaining the balance and your CIBIL score is
good, then you will never be asked for
any document or
income proof related to the loan, after looking at
your balance in the account,
you may start getting loan offers like credit
card, you may take a personal loan  Whether it's a business loan or a
home loan, all these types of loan
offers are visible. So, if you're
planning your investment this way, then
you won't find a better option than ICC Bank. This is the best
option for you today. ICC
Bank has roaming accounts,
so you can open an account anywhere and avail
services anywhere. Such banks offer interest rates
in one place. They have more than 5,000
branches in India, so you can
go to any branch and avail the service. Their advantage is
that they have ATM
machines for around Rs 15,000. You can
use the modern ATM machine of any bank today.
Any bank is a good example,
it is a reward, so you can use that too.
Now let's talk about their account
variant, the Wealth Management Account. If
you maintain good money and
maintain a good profile, then you
can use the Contra Voucher on their website.
For this, there is a special Adampur Voucher, which keeps
you updated with all the investment news.
So you don't need to
go there and ask any financial
related information from any party. The
bank itself, the bank
officer who has your SIM, will keep
guiding you as to what is happening in the market today,
where should you invest, whether
in shares or in Muzaffarpur.
This is
not the entire account, just like a financial account,
you have complete control over it. If you want,
you can get a bank account opened and have complete
control over where the investment should be made.
Big professionals have a
private banking account here. After this, there is a private banking account in ICC Bank, if you are
high profile, now
you can open such an account which has another
access to your account, which cannot see the limit or purse.
For this,
you can also open a private bank loan account with them, which is
your bill recovery, but
behind you is all your investment,
your relation SIM, which is inside the marriage, will
maintain everything for you
and will give you Detroit Forest Service, so
this is also related to the account,
after that their current account
balance is Agya Chakra Trident, but
you  If you are a businessman or a corporator, you
can open a current account with ICC Bank.
What ICC Bank has in this current account is a
smart engine account.
If you wish, you can run your account according to your recording.
They have a
smart cut in the middle, hence the
name Smart Vijay
Account. What is inside it? If your
balance is running high, if you want to
transfer more, then you
can make commitments accordingly. This is what they have in the world.
After this, their startup current account is the
best current account. Today, if you are
setting up new companies in coastal areas, you will
not be able to manage your money because
after the investment, there are many plants in it, that you have to
set up your office, take rest, prepare
all the computer purchase work,
so what happens at that time is that ICC Bank
gives you relief. In that startup current
account, you have to do any maintenance simultaneously. If you
are a startup, then you can
go to ICC Bank's startup current account. So,
1 inch is the best option like
or you can open a smart minute current account.  If you have an account, then
in this also they have given an option that
if your card gets activated on this platform for six months,
if it does not get activated for 6 months, then it
gives you time to understand yourself. In this,
if you take time from the bank, then after 6 minutes you
do proper maintenance of the account and
till the end you understand everything,
this is in their current account in VS
and their payment is done from the account, the
magistrate and bench of import and export are separate, so in that
also you can know about these
current accounts. Friends have many types
of accounts with ICC Bank, which you can
use if you are a businessman,
their best offer is CMS related,
payment collection related services are the best
option today, there is color QR code payment
collection, you can use it on ATM India and their marriage rules,
but
if you use bank barcode and if you use it then
your school is more secure, for this
you can open an account with ICC Bank and use it,
which is different from Paytm
or if you are using it from any bank  If you have an ID, you
can use ICICI Bank ID,
which is necessary. Aadhar is something, then
your bank and PAC details will be inside it. In case of
any problem, you will find a school here. If
you have a POS machine or a
retail shop, then
you can also avail services related to the machine. If
you have some work for payment collection, then there is a
facility of ICICI Bank ID,
like payment gateway, first payment
collection also. They have many types of
services and ID is entered, so there are
business related accounts. After that, let's
talk about investment. Their
wife initial plan has good investment
options in it. They have a plan for children.
They have a citizen pension plan, so
if you enter an ID, then
you will get investment options for it.
After this, what about health policy,
their group companies provide this number to
help and
within this, you can get health
policy for your family. You can get senior citizen policy. They provide
this policy for people between Rs 2805 to Rs 1000.  So you
can go to April policy, after this their
group company is such a diet, there are
many ways in the share market that they have offers in
Malaysia Pune, if you start investing then the
extreme brokers also have demat
account, they say in two in one account, then
you can
go to the service, you can study through all types of
loans, home loan,
business loan and personal loan,
so my final opinion is that if you
go to ICC Bank, then you get many types of
services inside the cave, so
if you want to use a new bank, I
just want to do it and want to open a new account, then
when you open this, you must check out the services of ICC Bank
and they have put everything online too, so they are available
online too and
I will also put the link of ICC Bank's website for you in this mission of yours in the video,
so by
going there
you can see the details service of Khesari Bank, so stay tuned to the video,
thank you very much, thank you, please like
and subscribe.